centerd.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy - Centerd.com (first draft)

**Center'd Privacy Policy**

Center'd takes your privacy seriously. To learn more about our Privacy Policy, please read the information below. The following terms and conditions are integrated into each user experience on Center'd and shall govern all privacy issues on this site. We are committed to protecting the privacy rights of our users, while creating a safe and open forum for community members to express themselves in a positive, constructive manner. 

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or services. By using the Center'd website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. When you provide personal information through our website, the information may be sent to servers located in the United States and other countries around the world. For practical tips from the federal government and the technology industry to help you be on guard against Internet fraud, secure your computer, and protect your personal information, [click here](http://onguardonline.gov/index.html). 

**Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information or to the settings for your Center'd account at any time, by logging in to your account on the Center'd website and editing the information on your Profile page. You can also send a request to close your account on the Center'd website. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. 

**Information**

You should be sure that anything you post on Center'd is acceptable for public display on our site and via other methods such as search engines. Information collected by Center'd from the site (such as, for example, patterns of utilization) is exclusively owned by Center'd. This information can be utilized by Center'd in such manner as Center'd, at its sole discretion, deems appropriate. 

**Customized Content**

Information you provide at registration or in your profile section is also used to customize your experience on the web site. For example, when you login to your account we may display the names of new users who have recently joined your network. 

**Communications**

Center'd may send you service-related messages based on activity on the site. For instance, if someone in your network sends you a message on the site, we may send you an email. Center'd may also send you information about new product features or invitations to participate in research surveys unless you have opted-out of receiving these types of messages. Registered users can control which type of service-related and product-related messages you receive on the "Settings" page [here](http://www.centerd.com/my/account.aspx). 

Although you may opt-out of service-related messages, Center'd reserves the right to send you messages related to your account, or administrative-related emails even if you opt-out of all voluntary email notifications. 

**Information Sharing**

Center'd takes the privacy of our users very seriously. Registered users of Center'd can adjust their privacy preferences from the 'My Center' page [here](http://www.centerd.com/my/privacy.aspx). However, Center'd does not control whether or how quickly third-party search engines may or may not update their index or cache. We may provide non-personally identifiable data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. 

**Communications Between Users**

In emails you initiate through Center'd, for example an invitation sent to a non-user, we will list your email address and name in the header of the message. Some other communications that you initiate through the Center'd website, like a request for contact, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal contact information. Your contact information typically will only be shared if you have disclosed it to the recipient through action on our Site. 

**Information about your Contacts**

In order to invite others to connect with you directly in Center'd, you may enter their names and email addresses. This information will be used by Center'd to send your invitation, any messages that you may write, reminders, and any event-related messages. 

**Use of Cookies and Other Technologies to Collect Information**

We use various technologies to collect information from your computer and about your activities on our site. Like the information you enter at registration or in your profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site. 

\- **Information collected automatically.** We automatically collect information from your browser when you visit our website. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us (see "Cookies" below), and the referring website address. In addition, Center'd tracks edits, history and changes to any profile by users of our site. 

\- **Cookies.** When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. For example, when you sign in to our website, we will record your user ID, information to identify your computer, and the name on your user or member account in the cookie file on your computer. We also may record your password in this cookie file, if you indicated that you would like your password saved for automatic sign-in. For security purposes, we will encrypt the account ID and password that we store in such cookies. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our website.

\- **Other Technologies.** We may use standard Internet technology, such as pixel tags, web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our site. We also may include web beacons in promotional or other e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our website visitors to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, or other activities.

\- **Information collected by third-party advertising companies** We may allow third-party advertising companies, including ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt-out of ad targeting from member companies [(www.networkadvertising.org)](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Partnering with Other Organizations to Offer Combined Services**

Center'd may partner with other online services to give you the combined results of both services. Whenever we offer such combined services, it will be your choice to make use of the combined services or not. In these cases, your personally identifiable information will only be passed from Center'd to the partner, if you choose to use the combined service. In that case, you accept that the privacy policy of our partner will apply to its use of your data. 

**Offensive speech**

Center'd shall remove, and requests each user of Center'd to flag for removal, any offensive speech in the form of text, pictures, audio, and/or video posted on Center'd, including that which is obscene, pornographic, spiteful, inciteful of hatred or illegal activity, libelous, slanderous, and/or inflammatory. 

**Children and Minors**

Center'd is not for children under the age of 13. Center'd does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13, nor allow anyone under the age of 13 to register. If we learn that we have collected personal information from anyone under the age of 13, we will remove that information as quickly as possible. If you believe we might have personal information about anyone under the age of 13, please contact us at [privacy@centerd.com](mailto:privacy@centerd.com). 

**Legal Disclaimer**

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required to do so by law. We will disclose personal information when we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company, to protect ourselves or any other person, to exercise our legal rights, or to defend against legal claims. 

**Security**

In effort to secure your personal information, access to your data on Center'd is password-protected. In addition, we use encryption in the transmission of your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Center'd may update this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site and/or send you an email. Unless stated otherwise, our updated Privacy Policy shall apply to all information that we have about you and your account. 

**Contact information**

If you have any questions or concerns about the Center'd Privacy Policy, please email us at [privacy@centerd.com](mailto:privacy@centerd.com). You may also contact us by mail at the following address: 

Center'd Corporation   
4400 Bohannon Drive, Suite 100  
Menlo Park, CA 94025   

If you have any suggestions for us, please use our feedback page.
